Ashley Borkowicz Support Hero / Product Specialist

Passionate about programming and providing a great UX. Madly in love with Python and Linux, interested in functional programming. Flexible and empathetic, they're always up for a new challenge.

This resume looks better in the browser! Take a look here: https://ashbork.github.io/astro_resume/en/

Professional Experience

LiveChat Inc

Support Hero / Product Specialist 2022-06 - 2023-03-01

9 months

Real-time customer service, technical troubleshooting and automation of internal processes with use of Python and JS. Close cooperation with the HelpDesk development team, UXR, collection and analysis of customer feedback.

- · 'Customer advocate' of 2022 nominee
- Reached ~95% CSAT due to expert knowledge and great attitude
- Reduced the resolution time of internal issues with HelpDesk by ~60%
- · Created multiple technical articles in the internal wiki, detailing processes and workflows

LiveChat Inc

Frontend Developer 2023-03 - ongoing

1 yr 2 mths

Development of the HelpDesk product in close collaboration with the team. Participation in the process of designing and brainstorming new and existing functionalities. Technological stack: TypeScript (TS), React, Redux, Jest. Additionally, working on an internal CRM system using Vue and Vuex.

- Assisted in getting HelpDesk to cross 1000 paying customers
- Introduced new versions of React and the internal Design System to the product
- Improved internal processes and tools, improving the team's productivity

Education

Technikum nr 7 im. Polskich Zwycięzców Enigmy Wrocław

IT specialist 2017-09 - 2021-06

- EE.08 Montaż i eksploatacja systemów komputerowych, urządzeń peryferyjnych i sieci (Installation and utilization of computer systems, peripherals and networks)
- EE.09 Programowanie, tworzenie i administrowanie stronami internetowymi i bazami danych (Programming, building and administrating websites and databases)

Uniwersytet Adama Mickiewicza w Poznaniu

Computer Science 2023-10 - ongoing

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux
- Jest
- React Query
- Vue
- Vuex
- · Python w/ mypy

- Flask
- Git
- Linux
- UXR
- Technical writing

Languages

- Polish Native
- English C1